<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Memoizations</title>
    <link>http://peterj35.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Memoizations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>By Peter Ju</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 14:08:18 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://peterj35.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Solving the user acquisition problem</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/solving-the-user-acquisition-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 14:08:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/solving-the-user-acquisition-problem/</guid>
      <description>You can build it but will they come?
 In all my 8 years of building software, the biggest challenge is never building the software itself. It&amp;rsquo;s to get real users to actually use it.
 If a tree falls in a forest and nobody&amp;rsquo;s around to hear it, does it make a sound? Alternatively, if a website is published to the internet and nobody visits it, did it make a difference?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Mobile First</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/mobile-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 16:20:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/mobile-first/</guid>
      <description>With Pickr, one of the front end engineering philosophies I decided early on was to only design with an extreme mobile first mentality. Mobile first design refers to a design philosophy that aims to create better UX by starting the design process from the smallest of screens, which is mobile. Extreme mobile first refers to a design philosophy where every other design other than mobile is de-prioritized.
I made this assumption since I imagine most people visiting Pickr will experience mobile, and mobile only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Record</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/what-to-record/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 01:16:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/what-to-record/</guid>
      <description>I really enjoy learning things, which I hope everyone on our planet can attest to, so more uniquely, I like teaching people about those things. That&amp;rsquo;s something that really gets me motivated and fulfilled at the end of the day, it&amp;rsquo;s been the case since in my professional life explaining things to coworkers, the case when I was a TA back in university, or when I was tutoring kids English back in Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biking With Classical Music</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/biking-with-classical-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 02:28:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/biking-with-classical-music/</guid>
      <description>Biking  “It’s just a massive challenge. We’re in business to sell bicycles… and we have no bicycles.
 Michael Cranwell, general manager at Gears Bike Shop
Another way that Canada, and other parts of the world has changed since the outbreak of the Coronavirus disease, is the rise of recreational bikers.
Biking, even pre-pandemic has always had a special place in my heart. It is simply the best way to explore and navigate a new area for pleasure, if the conditions are suitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Reopen</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/gradual-reopen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 02:59:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/gradual-reopen/</guid>
      <description>Yet another strategy for restaurants to maximize patrons given the constraints during the panedemic, has been outdoor partios which have been converted from parking lots.
Just yesterday, a partial reopen phase began in Ontario, including the reopening of outdoor patios. One interesting difference between this reopen and the previous ones is the fact that last calls have been set back to pre-pandemic times (2AM), as opposed to the brutally tight 9PM in the previous reopen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Pickr</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/introducing-pickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 22:41:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/introducing-pickr/</guid>
      <description>What is Pickr? It is a tournament style game that can be played online. Players select a topic (or more commonly, may click on a link to find one) for the tournament to be based upon. When the game is opened, users are shown 2 random choices that are essentially contestants for the given topic.
I pick the Pomeranian, as I&amp;#39;m biased towards breeds with longer furThe player continues to play until only the victor remains, in continuous rounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
