<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>talk on SWPJ</title>
    <link>http://peterj35.github.io/tags/talk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in talk on SWPJ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Peter Ju © all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 22:50:37 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://peterj35.github.io/tags/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basic Product Analytics</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/basic-analytics.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 22:50:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/basic-analytics.md/</guid>
      <description>The beauty of having something (relatively) complete and available to the general public, is that it can get some legs of its own, and have some exciting moments.
Pickr has had two big moments in the last half a year, which led me to finally implement some basic Amplitude user tracking.
One moment was 6 months ago, which was the post Dream SMP member Tournament. There was a post on reddit which got somewhat popular, and brought a lot of new users to the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Record</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/what-to-record/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 01:16:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/what-to-record/</guid>
      <description>Learning new things are a great pleasure of mine, but even more than that sometimes is the act of spreading this joy by teaching others. That&amp;rsquo;s something that really gets me motivated and fulfilled at the end of the day, it&amp;rsquo;s been the case since in my professional life explaining things to coworkers, the case when I was a TA back in university, or when I was tutoring kids English back in Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biking With Classical Music</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/biking-with-classical-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 02:28:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/biking-with-classical-music/</guid>
      <description>Biking  “It’s just a massive challenge. We’re in business to sell bicycles… and we have no bicycles.
 Michael Cranwell, general manager at Gears Bike Shop
Another way that Canada, and other parts of the world has changed since the outbreak of the Coronavirus disease, is the rise of recreational bikers.
Biking, even pre-pandemic has always had a special place in my heart. It is simply the best way to explore and navigate a new area for pleasure, if the conditions are suitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Reopen</title>
      <link>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/gradual-reopen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 02:59:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://peterj35.github.io/posts/gradual-reopen/</guid>
      <description>Yet another strategy for restaurants to maximize patrons given the constraints during the panedemic, has been outdoor partios which have been converted from parking lots.
Just yesterday, a partial reopen phase began in Ontario, including the reopening of outdoor patios. One interesting difference between this reopen and the previous ones is the fact that last calls have been set back to pre-pandemic times (2AM), as opposed to the brutally tight 9PM in the previous reopen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
